Warriors. Conquerors. Heroes.
The Barbarians is a adventure, fantasy, action film directed by Ruggero Deodato.
Orphaned brothers Kutchek and Gore are adopted by a tribe
led by Canary the owner of a powerful jewel.
The evil Kadar wants both Canary and the jewel.
Attacking the tribe he kidnaps Canary but the stone eludes him.
The brothers are taken to be trained as gladiators and
years later have grown to be VERY big.
They escape and set off on a quest to find the jewel and rescue Canary.
Kutchek, played by Peter Paul.
Gore, played by David Paul.
Kadar, played by Richard Lynch.
Kara/Ismene, played by Eva LaRue.
Canary, played by Virginia Bryant.
China, played by Sheeba Alahani.
The Barbarians is a 1987 sword and sorcery film directed by Ruggero Deodato and starring
the Barbarian Brothers (Peter and David Paul), Richard Lynch and Eva La Rue.
The film is an Italian and American co-production
shot in Rome and the Abruzzo Mountains.
Peter and David Paul were nominated for a Golden Raspberry Award for Worst
New Star for this film at the 8th Golden Raspberry Awards.
The film explores themes of dragon, barbarian, twins, jewel, sword and sorcery.